<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.teopost.GDriveSync</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>GDrive Sync</name>
  <summary>Bidirectional Google Drive synchronization for GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Sincronizzazione bidirezionale con Google Drive per GNOME</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Synchronisation bidirectionnelle avec Google Drive pour GNOME</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      GDrive Sync keeps a local folder synchronized with your Google Drive.
      Files live on your disk, so every application can use them; a background
      service propagates changes in both directions using rclone.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="it">
      GDrive Sync mantiene una cartella locale sincronizzata con Google Drive.
      I file restano sul disco, utilizzabili da qualsiasi applicazione; un
      servizio in background propaga le modifiche in entrambe le direzioni
      tramite rclone.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">
      GDrive Sync maintient un dossier local synchronisé avec Google Drive.
      Les fichiers restent sur le disque, utilisables par toute application ;
      un service en arrière-plan propage les modifications dans les deux sens
      via rclone.
    </p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.teopost.GDriveSync.desktop</launchable>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/teopost/gsync-drive</url>
  <developer id="io.github.teopost">
    <name>Stefano Teodorani</name>
  </developer>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="0.4.2" date="2026-07-05">
      <description>
        <p>The Drive folder selection can now be changed after setup from
        the account preferences; applying a change realigns the
        synchronization automatically.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.1" date="2026-07-05">
      <description>
        <p>Fix the first synchronization of a new account failing when
        bisync state from a removed account or a previous installation was
        still on disk.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.4.0" date="2026-07-05">
      <description>
        <p>Setup wizard reworked: the first page only connects the Google
        account; a new page shows the Drive folders as a checkbox tree with
        per-folder sizes, so several folders can be selected for
        synchronization. The interface is now translated (English, French,
        Italian) following the system language.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.3.0" date="2026-07-04">
      <description>
        <p>Multiple Google accounts; the first sync runs in the background
        service and closing the setup window offers to continue it in the
        background.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.2.0" date="2026-07-04">
      <description>
        <p>Initial sync progress bar with on-demand details; pick the Drive
        folder to synchronize by browsing it.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="0.1.0" date="2026-07-04">
      <description>
        <p>Initial release.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
</component>
